Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Works by Susan Sontag, 1945-2004
  - Sub-series 6.2, 1960-2004; 113 boxes (56.50 lin. ft.) and 12 oversize boxes
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 175, Folder 12)
      US press. 7 items.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 176, Folder 1)
      Penguin UK edition correspondence, jacket design and copy with holograph corrections. 20 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 2)
      UK press. 46 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 3)
      Germany press. 55 pages and 1 item.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 4)
      Germany press. 44 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 5)
      Arab translation correspondence. 7 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2004. (Box 176, Folder 6)
      Farsi translation correspondence. 2 items.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Chinese translation correspondence. 1 item.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Spain press and Barcelona publicity trip. 70 pages and 19 items. Includes correspondence from Robert Wilson
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Spanish translation correspondence and drafts with holograph corrections. 140 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 176, Folder 10)
      Spanish translation correspondence and drafts with holograph corrections. 126 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Italy press. 5 pages and 2 items.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 177, Folder 1)
      Brazil press; Portugese translation correspondence and draft with holograph corrections. 133 pages and 1 item.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 177, Folder 2)
      France press. 10 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 177, Folder 3)
      French translation correspondence and drafts with holograph corrections. 148 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003. (Box 177, Folder 4)
      Appearance at Kelly Writers House, University of Pennsylvania. 5 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., no date. (Box 177, Folder 5)
      Amnesty International Lecture research material. 18 items.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2001, no date. (Box 177, Folder 6)
      Amnesty International Lecture drafts (War and Photography). 104 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., no date. (Box 177, Folder 7)
      Amnesty Lecture final drafts (one with introduction). 52 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., no date. (Box 177, Folder 8)
      Amnesty Lecture for the American Academy in Berlin published by Oxford University Press. 85 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 177, Folder 9)
      Excerpt in New Yorker. 74 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 177, Folder 10)
      Excerpt in New Yorker. 111 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002, 2003. (Box 177, Folder 11)
      Excerpt in New Yorker and republication in The Guardian. 104 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2003, no date. (Box 178, Folder 1)
      Commentary in Diogene. 81 pages and 1 item.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., no date. (Box 178, Folder 2)
      Typescript draft pages with holograph corrections; holograph and typescript notes, research material, book proposal. 74 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., no date. (Box 178, Folder 3)
      Typescript draft and query pages with holograph corrections; holograph notes. 85 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 178, Folder 4)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs with holograph corrections. 140 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002, no date. (Box 178, Folder 5)
      Typescript drafts with holograph corrections; photocopied excerpt. 78 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 178, Folder 7)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs with holograph corrections ("Final Pass"). 140 pages.
    - Regarding the Pain of Others., 2002. (Box 178, Folder 8)
      Typescript draft with holograph corrections. 110 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2000-2001, no date. (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Typescript drafts of contents, front matter, Where the Stress Falls essay with holograph corrections; correspondence; photocopies of essays in original published formats; draft notes. 158 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2000-2001, no date. (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Typescript drafts of acknowledgements and essays Where the Stress Falls, Thirty Years Later with holograph corrections; copies of essays in original published formats; research material. 122 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2000-2001, no date. (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Correspondence; typescript drafts of contents, acknowledgements, essays with holograph corrections; draft of part one comprised of copies of essays in original published formats. 173 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 179, Folder 4)
      Draft of part two comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 92 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Draft of part three comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 124 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001, no date. (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Correspondence; faxed proof pages with holograph corrections; draft of first half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 140 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Draft of second half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 140 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 180, Folder 1)
      Photocopy of draft of first half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 162 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 180, Folder 2)
      Photocopy of draft of second half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript. 153 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 180, Folder 3)
      Photocopy of draft of first half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript with holograph copyedits. 172 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 180, Folder 4)
      Photocopy of draft of second half comprised of photocopies of essays in original published format or typescript with holograph copyedits. 150 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., no date. (Box 180, Folder 5)
      Galley pages and fax of galley pages with holograph corrections; draft of acknowledgements; fax of contents pages. 41 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 180, Folder 6)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of first half with new holograph corrections in red. 172 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 180, Folder 7)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of second half with new holograph corrections in red. 195 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 1)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of first half with holograph corrections ("First Pass Pages Master"). 174 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 2)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of second half with holograph corrections ("First Pass Pages Master"). 195 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 3)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of first half with new holograph corrections in pencil, red, and green ("An's set"). 172 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 4)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of second half with new holograph corrections in pencil, red, and green ("An's set"). 195 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 5)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of various pages from first half with new holograph corrections. 177 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 181, Folder 6)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of various pages from second half with new holograph corrections. 182 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 1)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of first half with new holograph corrections in red ("first pass"). 172 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 2)
      Photocopy of Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of second half with new holograph corrections in red ("first pass"). 194 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 3)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of first half with holograph corrections ("Final Pass"). 172 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 4)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux page proofs of second half with holograph corrections ("Final Pass"). 191 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 5)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux various page proofs with holograph corrections ("Final Pass"). 64 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 6)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux jacket copy drafts; sample pages; correspondence; catalog. 33 pages and 1 item.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 7)
      Farrar, Straus & Giroux book design. 12 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001, 2002. (Box 182, Folder 8)
      Homage to Halliburton: correspondence. 14 pages and 2 items.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 182, Folder 9)
      Wisdom Project: draft and galleys with holograph corrections. 50 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001, 2004. (Box 183, Folder 1)
      Germany. 7 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2002-2003, no date. (Box 183, Folder 2)
      Spain. 27 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 1991. (Box 183, Folder 3)
      Italy. 7 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2002, no date. (Box 183, Folder 4)
      France. 9 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 5)
      US publicity. 9 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 6)
      US reviews. 49 pages and 4 items.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001-2002. (Box 183, Folder 7)
      UK publicity and reviews.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001-2002. (Box 183, Folder 8)
      UK reviews. 9 items.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 9)
      Excerpt in The New Yorker. 76 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 10)
      Excerpt in The New Yorker. 79 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 11)
      Excerpt in The New Yorker. 119 pages.
    - Where the Stress Falls., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 12)
      Excerpt in The New Yorker. 61 pages.
    - Alice in Bed., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 13)
      Chinese translation. 2 items.
    - Alice in Bed., 2000. (Box 183, Folder 14)
      Brazil. 1 item.
    - Alice in Bed., 1997-1998. (Box 183, Folder 15)
      Mexico. 6 items.
    - Alice in Bed., 2001. (Box 183, Folder 16)
      Finland. 7 pages.
    - Alice in Bed., 1999-2000. (Box 183, Folder 17)
      Holland. 41 pages.
    - Alice in Bed., 2000. (Box 183, Folder 18)
      Holland publicity materials. 8 items.
    - Alice in Bed., 2000. (Box 183, Folder 19)
      New York Theatre Workshop. 17 pages and 13 items.
    - Alice in Bed., 1997. (Box 183, Folder 20)
      Oak Street Theatre (Portland, Maine). 1 item.
    - Alice in Bed., 2004. (Box 183, Folder 21)
      American Drama (Alexander Press). 1 item.
    - Alice in Bed., 1995, 1998, 2000. (Box 183, Folder 22)
      Rosenstone/Wender Agency. 5 items.
    - Duet for Cannibals., ca. 1968. (Box 184, Folder 1)
      Notes and negatives. 4 pages and 34 items.
    - Duet for Cannibals., ca. 1968. (Box 184, Folder 2)
      Stills. Folder 1 of 2. ca. 75 items.
    - Duet for Cannibals., ca. 1968. (Box 184, Folder 3)
      Stills. Folder 2 of 2. ca. 75 items.
    - Pirandello and Kundera., 1980-1981. (Box 185)
      Come Tu Mi Vuoi: Torino publicity booklets and professional production and publicity photographs. 83 items. In large Kodak flat box
    - Gogol's Grandson., 1964, 1988. (Box 271, Folder 7)
      Review of Tommaso Landolfi's Gogol's Wife and Other Stories: clipping with holograph corrections, drafts, and later reprint. 2 items and 18 pages.
    - Yugoslav Report., 1965. (Box 271, Folder 8)
      Typescript draft with holograph corrections and photocopy of New York Review of Books draft with letter. 24 pages and 1 envelope.
    - Questions of Travel., ca. 1980-1985. (Box 272, Folder 10)
      Notes and typescript draft pages with holograph corrections, letter to editor. 29 pages and 1 folder. Published as Model Destinations. See Communism and the Intellectuals
    - Looking with Avedon., 1978. (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Can Rights Be Equal?., 1976. (Box 272, Folder 12)
      Typescript first draft with holograph corrections and photocopy of draft and Vogue galleys with holograph corrections. 21 pages.
    - On Translation., 1982. (Box 272, Folder 13)
      Talk at the American Academy, Rome. Two varying typescript drafts. 7 pages.
    - Art of Passage (An)., 1981. (Box 272, Folder 14)
      Preface to Marilu Eustachio exhibit catalog. Notes, typescript drafts with holograph corrections, clipping. 9 pages.
    - Mr. Balanchine., 1983. (Box 272, Folder 15)
      Notes, typescript draft with holograph corrections, and Vanity Fair galleys with holograph corrections. 13 pages.
    - Images of People Past., 1984. (Box 272, Folder 16)
      Proust. Typescript drafts with holograph corrections. 14 pages and 1 item.
    - Reuterswards Inter-World., 1982. (Box 272, Folder 17)
      Typescript English language drafts with holograph notes and corrections. 20 pages.
    - Tales of Chekhov., ca. 1980-1989. (Box 272, Folder 18)
      Long blurb for Volume 6: The Witch and Other Stories. Typescript drafts with holograph corrections. 5 pages and 1 item.
    - Hungarian Samizdat., 1986. (Box 272, Folder 19)
      Typescript draft with holograph corrections and poster for book. 2 pages and 2 items.
    - Questions of Travel., ca. 1980-1985. (Box 275, Folder 3)
      Notes and typescript drafts with holograph corrections. 97 pages and 1 folder. Includes draft pages for a related Intellectuals story. Related to Communism and the Intellectuals essay
    - Questions of Travel., ca. 1980-1985. (Box 275, Folder 5)
      Notes, typescript drafts with holograph corrections, letter. 69 pages. Includes draft pages for a related Intellectuals story. Related to Communism and the Intellectuals essay
    - Woman's Beauty: Put-Down or Power Source? (A)., 2001. (Box 275, Folder 9)
      Permissions request. 1 page. Attached unendorsed check returned to Sontag estate
    - Woman's Beauty: Put-Down or Power Source? (A)., 1975. (Box 275, Folder 10)
      Article clippings. 2 items.
    - Beauty: How will it Change Next?., 1975. (Box 275, Folder 11)
      Article clippings. 3 items.
    - Susan Sontag Reader (A)., 1982-1983. (Box 275, Folder 12)
      Publicity and reviews. 7 items.
    - Susan Sontag Reader (A)., ca. 1982. (Box 275, Folder 13)
      Draft of introduction by Elizabeth Hardwick. 4 pages and 1 envelope.
    - Witnessing., 2001. (Box 276, Folder 3)
      Don McCullin introduction. Correspondence with Mark Holborn, typescript drafts with holograph corrections, and contract. 37 pages.
    - Politics and the Novel., 2000. (Box 276, Folder 4)
      For Los Angeles Times Book Review symposium. Correspondence with Steve Wasserman, typescript drafts and galleys with holograph corrections. 11 pages.
    - Thinking about the Sixth., 2004. (Box 276, Folder 5)
      For 10 Commandments exhibit catalog. Correspondence, typescript drafts and proofs, contract, and clippings. 35 pages and 12 items.
    - W., 1990-1991. (Box 276, Folder 6)
      For Hockney's Alphabet. Correspondence with Stephen Spender, drafts with holograph corrections, image of artwork, copies of other's pieces for book, publicity and event material. 40 pages.
    - 1926 Pasternak, Tsvetayeva, Rilke., 2001. (Box 276, Folder 7)
      Faxed galleys with holograph corrections and published copy of Sontag's preface in Los Angeles Times Book Review with title The Sacred Delirium of Art. 10 pages and 1 item.
    - 1926 Pasternak, Tsvetayeva, Rilke., 2000, 2001, 2003. (Box 276, Folder 8)
      Correspondence and contracts regarding book preface with New York Review of Books. 7 items.
    - 1926 Pasternak, Tsvetayeva, Rilke., ca. 2001. (Box 276, Folder 9)
      Draft and galley of book sections. 27 pages. Annotated by Sontag
    - 1926 Pasternak, Tsvetayeva, Rilke., 2001. (Box 276, Folder 10)
      Notes, correspondence with Edwin Frank, fact-checking by Peter Perrone, galleys and drafts with holograph corrections. 87 pages.
    - Writing as Reading., 2000-2001. (Box 276, Folder 11)
      For New York Times Writing on Writing series. Correspondence, drafts and anthology galleys with holograph corrections, copies of foreign and english language publication. 86 pages and 4 items.
    - Outlandish., 2004. (Box 276, Folder 12)
      Halldor Laxness introduction. Correspondence, notes, drafts with holograph corrections, research material. 129 pages.
    - Outlandish., 1972. (Box 276, Folder 13)
      Research material: Halldor Laxness. Christianity at Glacier (Reykjavik: Helgafell). Annotated and signed by Sontag. Clippings, post-its, and other placeholders inserted
    - Outlandish., no date. (Box 276, Folder 14)
      Research material: Jules Verne. Journey to the Centre of the Earth (London: Penguin Group). Annotated by Sontag
    - Singleness., 1993-1994. (Box 277, Folder 1)
      Neo-Borges text for Who's Writing This? Notations on the Authorial I. Correspondence, drafts and galleys with holograph corrections, notes. 74 pages.
    - Buchbilderbuch., 1995-1997. (Box 277, Folder 2)
      Correspondence with Quint Buchholz and Michael Kruger, image of illustration, draft with holograph corrections. 9 pages.
    - For Christopher Schotterer., 1986. (Box 277, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Hanser Verlag and drafts with holograph corrections. 16 pages.
    - Tribute from a Fellow Actor (A)., 2003. (Box 277, Folder 4)
      For Michael Kruger's 60th birthday. Correspondence and drafts with holograph corrections. 11 pages.
    - Lee Krasner Eulogy., ca. 1984. (Box 277, Folder 5)
      Talk. Draft pages and notes. 3 pages.
    - Bob is Sixty and We Praise Him., 1989-1990. (Box 277, Folder 6)
      For Bob Silvers birthday book. Correspondence and drafts with holgraph corrections. 13 pages.
    - Letters to the Editor., 1981, 1987, 1981, 1989. (Box 277, Folder 7)
      Various drafts with holograph corrections. 6 pages.
    - Best American Essays (The)., 1992-1993. (Box 277, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, publicity and reviews, introduction galleys and flap copy drafts with holograph corrections. 35 pages.
    - Best American Essays (The)., 1991-1992. (Box 277, Folder 9)
      Correspondence, selection lists, research material, copies of some essays in original published format, cover design, introduction drafts. 141 pages.
    - Best American Essays (The)., 1992. (Box 277, Folder 10)
      Notes, holograph and typescript drafts with holograph corrections. 127 pages.
    - Octavio Paz., 1998. (Box 277, Folder 11)
      For Los Angeles Times Book Review memoriam symposium. Correspondence with Steve Wasserman, drafts with holograph corrections, faxed galley, and article. 13 pages and 1 item.
    - Looking at the Unbearable., 1994. (Box 277, Folder 12)
      Goya text for Transforming Vision. Correspondence with Edward Hirsch and Art Institute of Chicago, contract, galleys, travel documents, notes, research material. 71 pages.
    - 240 Ecrivains Racontent une Journee du Monde., 1994. (Box 277, Folder 13)
      For Nouvel Observateur. Correspondence, holograph and typescript drafts. 71 pages.
    - Argument about Beauty., 2002. (Box 277, Folder 14)
      Correspondence, contract, final draft, galley. 19 pages.
    - I Remember Lucy., 2001. (Box 277, Folder 15)
      Correspondence, drafts with holograph corrections. 13 pages.
    - Conversation with Mikhail Baryshnikov., 2003. (Box 277, Folder 16)
      Contract, proof, and drafts with holograph corrections. 15 pages.
    - Nadas's Comedy of Internment., 2001. (Box 277, Folder 17)
      Introduction for Burial. Correspondence, proof with holograph corrections, and fax of play script. 34 pages.
    - Photography: a Little Summa., ca. 2003. (Box 277, Folder 18)
      Drafts with holograph corrections. 6 pages.
    - Photography: a Little Summa., 2003. (Box 277, Folder 19)
      Japanese photocriticism book correspondence. 8 pages.
    - Photography: a Little Summa., 2003. (Box 277, Folder 20)
      Spanish translation for El Cultural: correspondence and drafts with holograph notes. 10 pages.
    - At the Same Time., 2004. (Box 277, Folder 21)
      Nadine Gordimer lecture. Drafts with holograph corrections. 48 pages.
    - In Our Time, In This Moment., 2002, no date. (Box 277, Folder 22)
      4 pages.
    - Tokyo Art Jury., 2002. (Box 277, Folder 23)
    - World as India (The)., 2002-2003. (Box 278, Folder 1)
      St. Jerome Lecture on literary translation in memoriam W.G. Sebald. Drafts, notes and correspondence re Italian translation. 107 pages.
    - World as India (The)., 2003. (Box 278, Folder 2)
      Times Literary Supplement correspondence, proofs with holograph corrections, reviews. 9 pages.
    - World as India (The)., 2003. (Box 278, Folder 3)
      Spanish translation. 40 pages.
    - World as India (The)., 2003. (Box 278, Folder 4)
      Reactions. 5 pages.
    - Mind in Mourning (A)., 2000. (Box 278, Folder 5)
      Review of W.G. Sebald's Vertigo in Times Literary Supplement. Drafts and proofs with holograph corrections and correspondence. 56 pages.
    - Mind in Mourning (A)., 2000. (Box 278, Folder 6)
      For Los Angeles Times Book Review. 15 pages.
    - Mind in Mourning (A)., 2000. (Box 278, Folder 7)
      Spanish translation for Mexican magazine Nexos. 11 pages.
    - Book of the Year., 1996. (Box 278, Folder 8)
      Text on W.G. Sebald's Emigrants in Frankfurter Rundschau and other newspapers. Correspondence with Wolfram Schutte, draft, final published forms. 15 pages and 3 items.
    - Book of the Year., 1996. (Box 278, Folder 9)
      Italian translation. 16 pages and 1 item.
    - Book of the Year., 1996. (Box 278, Folder 10)
      Variant version in Times Literary Supplement. 5 pages.
    - The migr., 2002. (Box 278, Folder 11)
      Preface to W.G. Sebald's The Emigrants. 11 pages.
    - Exchange with Kenzaburo Oe., 1999, 2001. (Box 278, Folder 12)
      Original letters, copies, drafts with holograph corrections, other correspondence, published form. 67 pages and 1 item. See also Kazue Kobata correspondence file
    - Exchange with Kenzaburo Oe., 1999. (Box 278, Folder 13)
      Copies of letters between Oe and other correspondents. 12 items.
    - Exchange with Kenzaburo Oe., 2000. (Box 278, Folder 14)
      Spanish translation. 46 pages.
    - Exchange with Kenzaburo Oe., 2000. (Box 278, Folder 15)
      Publication in Yale Review. 53 pages. Post-its inserted
    - Exchange with Kenzaburo Oe., 1999. (Box 278, Folder 16)
      Publication in Micromega. 5 pages.
    - Double Destiny (A)., 2002-2004. (Box 278, Folder 17)
      Introduction to Anna Banti's Artemisia. Correspondence with Serpent's Tail, University of Nebraska Press, and Sarah Dunant. 21 items.
    - Double Destiny (A)., 2002-2004. (Box 278, Folder 18)